[{"question": " hey, pheebs! hi!", "answer": " hey. oh, oh, how'd it go?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " um, not so good. he walked me to the subway and said 'we should do this again!'", "answer": " ohh. ouch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " what? he said 'we should do it again', that's good, right?", "answer": " uh, no. loosely translated 'we should do this again' means 'you will never see me naked'.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " since when?", "answer": " since always. it's like dating language. y'know, like 'it's not you' means 'it is you'.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " or 'you're such a nice guy' means 'i'm gonna be dating leather-wearing alcoholics and complaining about them to you'.", "answer": " or, or, y'know, um, 'i think we should see other people' means 'ha, ha, i already am'.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " and everybody knows this?", "answer": " yeah. cushions the blow.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " yeah, it's like when you're a kid, and your parents put your dog to sleep, and they tell you it went off to live on some farm.", "answer": " that's funny, that, no, because, uh, our parents actually did, uh, send our dog off to live on a farm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " uh, ross.", "answer": " what? wh- hello? the millners' farm in connecticut? the millners, they had this unbelievable farm, they had horses, and, and rabbits that he could chase and it was- it w- .....oh my god, chi chi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " \"so how does it feel knowing you're about to die?\"", "answer": " \"warden, in five minutes my pain will be over. but you'll have to live with the knowledge that you sent an honest man to die.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " hey, that was really good!", "answer": " thanks! let's keep going.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " okay. \"so. whaddya want from me, damone, huh?\"", "answer": " \"i just wanna go back to my cell. 'cause in my cell, i can smoke.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " i think this is probably why damone smokes in his cell alone.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " not so much!", "answer": " whoah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " alright.. okay. no. give it to me.", "answer": " no no no, i am not giving you a cigarette.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " don't think of it as a cigarette. think of it as the thing that's been missing from your hand. when you're holding it, you feel right. you feel complete.", "answer": " y'miss it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " that's ridiculous!", "answer": " can i use.. either thumb?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": "  alright, don't tell me, don't tell me!  decaf cappucino for joey.. coffee black.. late.. and an iced tea. i'm getting pretty good at this!", "answer": " yeah. yeah, excellent.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " y'okay, phoebe?", "answer": " yeah- no- i'm just- it's, i haven't worked- it's my bank.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " what did they do to you?", "answer": " it's nothing, it's just- okay. i'm going through my mail, and i open up their monthly, you know, statement-", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " easy.", "answer": " - and there's five hundred extra dollars in my account.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " oh, satan's minions at work again...", "answer": " yes, 'cause now i have to go down there, and deal with them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " what are you talking about? keep it!", "answer": " it's not mine, i didn't earn it, if i kept it, it would be like stealing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " yeah, but if you spent it, it would be like shopping!", "answer": " okay. okay, let's say i bought a really great pair of shoes. do you know what i'd hear, with every step i took? 'not-mine. not-mine. not-mine.' and even if i was happy, okay, and, and skipping- 'not-not-mine, not-not-mine, not-not-mine, not-not-mine'...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " okay. i'd- just- i'd never be able to enjoy it. it would be like this giant karmic debt.", "answer": " chandler, what are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " oh! oh, god!", "answer": " what is this?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " i'm smoking. i'm smoking, i'm smoking.", "answer": " oh, i can't believe you! you've been so good, for three years!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " and this- is my reward!", "answer": " hold on a second, alright? just think about what you went through the last time you quit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " okay, so this time i won't quit!", "answer": " ohhh! put it out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " oh, no! i- i can't drink this now!", "answer": " alright. i'm gonna go change, i've got a date.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " this alan again? how's it goin'?", "answer": " 's'going pretty good, y'know? it's nice, and, we're having fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " so when do we get to meet the guy?", "answer": " let's see, today's monday... never.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " oh, come on! come on!", "answer": " no. not after what happened with steve.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " what are you talking about? we love schhteve! schhteve was schhexy!.. sorry.", "answer": " look, i don't even know how i feel about him yet. just give me a chance to figure that out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " well, then can we meet him?", "answer": " nope. schhorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " i mean, why should i let them meet him? i mean, i bring a guy home, and within five minutes they're all over him. i mean, they're like- coyotes, picking off the weak members of the herd.", "answer": " listen. as someone who's seen more than her fair share of bad beef, i'll tell you: that is not such a terrible thing. i mean, they're your friends, they're just looking out after you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " i know. i just wish that once, i'd bring a guy home that they actually liked.", "answer": " well, you do realise the odds of that happening are a little slimmer if they never get to meet the guy..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " let it go, ross.", "answer": " yeah, well, you didn't know chi chi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " do you all promise?", "answer": " yeah! we promise! we'll be good!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " hey, pheebs.", "answer": " 'dear ms. buffay. thank you for calling attention to our error. we have credited your account with five hundred dollars. we're sorry for the inconvenience, and hope you'll accept this-  -football phone as our free gift.' do you believe this?! now i have a thousand dollars, and a football phone!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " hey. it's him.  who is it?", "answer": " it's alan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " hi. alan, this is everybody. everybody, this is alan.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " hi, alan.", "answer": " i've heard schho much about all you guyschh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " c'mon!", "answer": " ...i'll go. let's start with the way he kept picking at- no, i'm sorry, i can't do this, can't do this. we loved him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " loved him! yeah! he's great!", "answer": " wait a minute! we're talking about someone that i'm going out with?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " and did you notice...?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": "  yeah.", "answer": " know what was great? the way his smile was kinda crooked.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " yes, yes! like the man in the shoe!", "answer": " ...what shoe?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " ...so i think alan will become the yardstick against which all future boyfriends will be measured.", "answer": " what future boyfriends? nono, i th- i think this could be, y'know, it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " really!", "answer": " oh, yeah. i'd marry him just for his david hasselhof impression alone. you know i'm gonna be doing that at parties, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " you know what i like most about him, though?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " the way he makes me feel about myself.", "answer": " yeah...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " hi.. how was the game?", "answer": " well..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " we won!! thank you! yes!", "answer": " fantastic! i have one question: how is that possible?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " alan.", "answer": " he was unbelievable. he was like that-that-that bugs bunny cartoon where bugs is playing all the positions, right, but instead of bugs it was first base-alan, second base-alan, third base-...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " i mean, it-it was like, it was like he made us into a team.", "answer": " yep, we sure showed those hassidic jewellers a thing or two about softball..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " can i ask you guys a question? d'you ever think that alan is maybe.. sometimes..", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " ..i dunno, a little too alan?", "answer": " well, no. that's impossible. you can never be too alan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " yeah, it's his, uh, innate alan-ness that-that-that we adore.", "answer": " i personally could have a gallon of alan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " hey, lizzie.", "answer": " hey, weird girl.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " i brought you alphabet soup.", "answer": " did you pick out the vowels?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " saltines?", "answer": " no, but would you like a thousand dollars and a football phone?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " what?  oh my god, there's really money in here.", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " weird girl, what are you doing?", "answer": " no, i want you to have it. i don't want it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " no, no, i ha-i have to give you something.", "answer": " oh, that's fine, no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " would you like my tin-foil hat?", "answer": " no. 'cause you need that. no, it's okay, thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " please, let me do something.", "answer": " okay, alright, you buy me a soda, and then we're even. okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " keep the change.  sure you don't wanna pretzel?", "answer": " no, i'm fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " eww!", "answer": " i know! i know, i opened it up and there it was, just floating in there, like this tiny little hitch-hiker!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " well, maybe it's a contest, y'know? like, collect all five?", "answer": " does, um, anyone wanna see?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " oh, hey, don't do that! cut it out!", "answer": " it's worse than the thumb!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " hey, this is so unfair!", "answer": " oh, why is it unfair?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " ...does the knuckle-cracking bother everybody?", "answer": " well, i-i could live without it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " oh, now, don't listen to him, pheebs, i think it's endearing.", "answer": " oh,  \"you do, do you\"?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " you know, there's nothing wrong with speaking correctly.", "answer": " \"indeed there isn't\"... i should really get back to work.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " yeah, 'cause otherwise someone might get what they actually ordered.", "answer": " ohh-ho-hooohhh. the hair comes out, and the gloves come on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " did you ever go out with a guy your friends all really like?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " okay.. well, i'm going out with a guy my friends all really like.", "answer": " waitwait.. we talking about the coyotes here? all right, a cow got through!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " can you believe it? ...y'know what? i just don't feel the thing. i mean, they feel the thing, i don't feel the thing.", "answer": " honey.. you should always feel the thing. listen, if that's how you feel about the guy, monica, dump him!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " i know.. it's gonna be really hard.", "answer": " well, he's a big boy, he'll get over it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " do you have any respect for your body?", "answer": " don't you realise what you're-you're doing to yourself?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " hey, y'know, i have had it with you guys and your cancer and your emphysema and your heart disease. the bottom line is, smoking is cool, and you know it.", "answer": "  chandler? it's alan, he wants to speak to you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": "  god, he's good.", "answer": " if only he were a woman.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " ooh, lambchop. how old is that sock? if i had a sock on my hand for thirty years it'd be talking too.", "answer": " okay. i think it's time to change somebody's nicotine patch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " hey. where's joey?", "answer": " joey ate my last stick of gum, so i killed him. do you think that was wrong?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " i think he's across the hall.", "answer": " thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": "  there y'go.", "answer": "  ooh, i'm alive with pleasure now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " hey pheebs, you gonna have the rest of that pop-tart?.. pheebs?", "answer": " does anyone want the rest of this pop-tart?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " hey, i might!", "answer": " sorry. ..y'know, those stupid soda people gave me seven thousand dollars for the thumb.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " you're kidding. oh my god.", "answer": " and on my way over here, i stepped in gum. ...what is up with the universe?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": "  what's going on?", "answer": " nothing. i just think it's nice when we're all here together.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " even nicer when everyone gets to wear their underwear..", "answer": " uh, joey..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": "  okay..", "answer": " oh! that was lambchop!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " please, guys, we have to talk.", "answer": " wait, wait, i'm getting a deja vu...no, i'm not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " alright, we have to talk.", "answer": " there it is!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " is there somebody else?", "answer": " no, nononono.. it's just.. things change. people change.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " we didn't change..", "answer": " so that's it? it's over? just like that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " look, i- i could go on pretending-", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " -but that wouldn't be fair to me, it wouldn't be fair to alan- it wouldn't be fair to you!", "answer": " who-who wants fair? y'know, i just want things back. y'know, the way they were.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " i'm sorry..", "answer": "  oh, she's sorry! i feel better!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": "  i just can't believe this! i mean, with the holidays coming up- i wanted him to meet my family-", "answer": " i'll meet somone else. there'll be other alans.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " oh, yeah! right!", "answer": " are you guys gonna be okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " hey hey, we'll be fine. we're just gonna need a little time.", "answer": "  i understand.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " wow.", "answer": " i'm, i'm really sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " yeah, i'm sorry too. but, i gotta tell you, i am a little relieved.", "answer": " relieved?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " remember when we went to central park and rented boats?.. that was fun.", "answer": " yeah. he could row like a viking.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " mmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " so how'd it go?", "answer": " oh, y'know..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " did he mention us?", "answer": " he said he's really gonna miss you guys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " ...that's it. i'm getting cigarettes.", "answer": " no no no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": "  i don't care, i don't care! game's over! i'm weak! i've gotta smoke! i've gotta have the smoke!", "answer": "  if you never smoke again i'll give you seven thousand dollars!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}]